



Sadra Shameli, Software Engineer

Full-Stack & Embedded engineer, based in Rotterdam, the Netherlands. My tech stack consists of TypeScript, React and Next.js together with tRPC, Prisma and NextAuth.js to develop intuitive web applications. I am also experienced in building robots and IoT devices.

Details	Driving license	Yes	Date of birth	11/12/2003
Links	https://sadra.nl https://geluidsvervuiling.eu		https://github.com/SadraShameli https://youtube.com/@SadraShameli	
Skills	TypeScript, React, Next.js TailwindCSS, Material UI tRPC, Prisma, NextAuth.js		ASP.NET, MVC, REST SQL Server, PostgreSQL C++, C#, Python	

Employment

Full-Stack engineer at Blue Star Planning, Rotterdam

December 2021 — January 2023

- Developed various IoT devices and 3D printing the casing. Intended to gather various data, such as sound recordings, loudness, temperature and humidity, air quality and RPM values. The sound recording go through IIR second-order section filtering and A-Weighting before saving. The devices are placed at different locations in Rotterdam.
- Developed the back-end to process the data gathered by the devices and developed
 the front-end at https://geluidsvervuiling.eu, where the sound recordings and
 loudness values are available depending on the device and it's location.

Salesman at Gamma, Den haag

February 2021 — Present

- Identified and maximized sales opportunities, and increased customer retention rates.
- Worked to ensure a positive and hassle-free customer experience.

Portfolio

Skills

- <u>ASP.NET</u>, Unit testing, SQL Server Management Studio and Azure Data Studio for database management. Familiar with REST API, Web API and MVC.
- TypeScript with React and Next.js, together with tRPC, Prisma and NextAuth.js to create SEO optimized and interactive websites. Familiar with SSR, SSG and CSR.

- Low level C C++ programming combined with Python for optimized embedded development.
- Relational databases such as PostgreSQL, SQL Server
- Working in Azure Cloud, Azure DevOps and GitHub environments.
- Ability to design 3D model with Fusion 360 and print with 3D printers.

Experience

- Developed an autonomous self-driving robot utilizing camera and Lidar scanner, with the ability to navigate through a variety of courses and avoid obstacles. In addition to the live camera feed, the robot offers remote control functionality through a console controller or via a website hosted on a local server. The source code for the robot is written in C++ and Python, utilizing TensorFlow for machine learning tasks, and is available at https://github.com/SadraShameli/ProjectAl
- Developing a graphics game engine from the ground up, using C++ and the DirectX 12 API featuring an interactive user interface built with ImGui. Able to create scenes, add cameras, and navigate freely within the game environment. Using an entity component system to add objects, set properties such as color, texture, and world position.
- Made an interactive Social Robot, designed the PCB and a suitable case using 3D printing.
 Assists low visioned people in walking safely.
- Achieved a third-place ranking at the provincial level in the Robocup competition in Iran.

Education	VWO - N&T, Grotius Collegie, Delft		
	September 2020 — July 2023		
Languages	O Persian Native speaker	0	English C2
	O Dutch C2		
Hobbies	Robotics Programming Photography Guitar Cars		